("She's A Genius" by Jet playing)
♪ My girl's ready to take control ♪
♪ She just blows my mind ♪
♪ She only listens to the radio ♪
♪ To see who's alive ♪
♪ They said, hey, there, girl... ♪
你被捕了！
You're under arrest!
你这个坏孩子
You bad, bad boy...
(gasping)
(whimpering)
(screaming)
海军罪案调查处 第七季第2集
重聚
Morning, Agent Fillmore.
早上好哦 Filmore探员
不错嘛 这绿色像军服一样
Ten-hut.
Like the Army greens.
我们的确专门处理海军罪案调查的
We do investigate crimes of the Navy here, though.
不错的笑容哦 我对美好事物一向有好品味 也许我猜 你对我没什么好感
Nice smile. Good thing I have a strong ego, or I'd think
you didn't like me.
What?
- 什么? - Ziva 她来过电话吗?
Ziva... did she call?
你也还没和她说过话 是吧?
You haven't spoken to her either, huh?
在飞机上想过 但是 呃 我也搞不清楚 情况有点...
Tried talking to her on the plane, but, uh...
I don't know.
Things got...
These details are classified.
这可都是机密信息 谢谢
Thank you.
- 没啦 不是啦 - 是的啦
- No, they're not. - They should be.
发生了什么啊?
What's going on around here anyway?
过安检时 我还得签名
I had to sign an autograph going through security.
I know what you mean.
我懂你意思 你认识心理服务部的Janice吗?
You know Janice in Psych Services?
男人的手? 漂亮的眼睛
Man hands? Great eyes.
对啊 她约我明晚出去喝一杯
Yeah. She asked me out for drinks tomorrow night.
对于一个上次出任务时 一半时间睡在地板上的人来讲 不错哦
That's not bad for a guy who spent half the last mission
- sleeping on the floor. - Was not sleeping
- 我才没睡在地板上 - 别想糊弄我
- on the floor. - Could have fooled me.
她准备好了自然会打来啊
She'll call when she's ready.
上次我这么讲时 可落得个被绑在北非的一把椅子上的下场
Last time I said that,
I ended up tied to a chair in North Africa.
她要回来了 对吧?
She's coming back, right?
嗯 她要回来了
Ah, she's coming back.
Course I don't know where she's gonna sit.
因为我也不知道她要坐哪里
(beep)
20块跟你赌到下个月底 那张桌子就没人了
20 bucks says that desk gonna be empty by the end of next month.
真不愿让你们失望
Hate to disappoint you.
我的辞职信
My letter of resignation.
Well, that's, uh, very long.
嗯 它还真是 呃 好长啊
I had a hard time choosing the right adjectives.
我一直很不知道该用哪个形容词
我拿不定主意是用幼稚 愣头青 还是烦人精
I couldn't decide between "childish,"
"juvenile," and just plain old "annoying."
- 说的没错 - 还有你...
It's true.
And you... you know better,
你没他那么遭 但你却做他狼狈为奸的同党
but you're so busy playing the faithful sidekick,
你跟他一路货色
you just go along for the ride.
好了 我受够了
Well, I've had enough.
Make sure that Agent Gibbs gets that.
确保Gibbs探员收到这个
(sighs)
- 太讨厌? - 同党?
- Annoying? - Sidekick?
ZIVA: Hello, Gibbs.
嗨 Gibbs 你的房门开着
Your door was open.
一直都是
Usually is.
我向你道歉 我迟到了
I, uh, apologize for being late.
我住的海军宿舍今早进行了临时演习 所以我...
The Navy lodge I was staying at ran a surprise drill
this morning, so I just...
这不重要
It's not important.
你好吗?
How are you?
还不错... Gibbs
I am fine... Gibbs.
That is what I wished
我有很多事想跟你说 这也是其中一件
to speak to you about, among other things.
首先... 我...
First of all, I...
wanted to say...
想和你说声谢谢
thank you.
Which hardly seems sufficient.
感觉一声谢谢远远不够
Considering so, I... It just called, um...
想到这些 我刚刚说了 呃...
一把古老的鹿皮榫眼凿
It's an old Buck mortise chisel.
这不是为了谢谢你救我 而是感谢你把我留在以色列
That is not for rescuing me.
That is for leaving me in Israel.
You're probably wondering,
- 你可能想知道 也许我只是突发奇想.. - 不
perhaps I rigged it to explode...
No.
我想 这真的是把好凿子
I was thinking this is a really nice chisel.
那时 呃...
When, uh...
你把我留在了以色列 我...
you left me in Israel,
I... I felt betrayed.
我觉得我被遗弃了
但是 我...
But I...
I had a long time to think about things.
我用了很长时间去思考
Very, very, very
非常 非常 非常长的时间
long time.
- 你把我留在那里是正确的 - 我知道
And you were right to leave me there.
I know.
嗯 关键是我也明白了
Well, the point is, now I do, too.
I had forgotten who I could trust.
我忘了 我可以信赖谁
We were a team, and I would like that again.
我们是一个团体 我想和从前一样
你得和主任谈谈
You need to talk to the director.
我是为你回来的
It is your blessing I came for.
(cell phone ringing)
(sighs)
Yeah.
DiNozzo 有什么消息?
DiNozzo, what do you got?
Uh-huh. Where?
哪里? 到时见
Meet you there.
Triple homicide.
是一起三重谋杀 你应该和Leon Vance谈谈
You need to talk to Leon Vance.
我已经告诉他 你会去见他
I already told him to expect you.
他不是你唯一要谈的人
And he's not the only one you need to talk to.
(camera shutter clicking)
嘿  你漏了照一张这里 同党
Hey, you missed a shot there, sidekick.
我可不是你的同党 Tony
I'm not your sidekick, Tony.
哦 你是的
And yet, you are.
No, I am not, because you're not the boss.
不 我可不是 你又不是老大
Gibbs不在 我就是老大
When Gibbs isn't here, I'm the boss.
- (camera shutter clicks) - Gibbs is here.
- Gibbs来了 - 嘿 老大
Hey, boss.
嗯 海军上士 Jeff Ross
Uh, Marine Staff Sergeant Jeff Ross.
他是订房的人
He's the one who booked the room.
说是为了朋友的婚前单身聚会
Said it was for a buddy's bachelor party.
本地警察确认了他的身份 通知了我们
Local LEOs identified him.
Then they called us.
另外两个还没确认身份
Haven't identified the other two yet.
还在等Duck那帮人
Still waiting on the Duck Man.
Who found him?
- 谁发现的他? - 是个脱衣舞女
That would be the stripper.
她和她的经理在另一个房间
She's in the next room with her manager.
(sighs)
Where is Fillmore?
Filmore在哪?
总算来了 我从凌晨三点就一直待在这
Finally. I've been here since 3:00 a.m.
你要赶着去其他地方吗?
You have someplace else you have to be?
不是我 是她
Not me, but her.
Scorpio是我最好的舞女
Scorpio's my best dancer.
听着 我一听说马上就赶来了
Listen, I got here as soon as I heard.
Hector Stuckey.
Hector Stuckey 我做秀场的
I'm in show biz.
好的... 你来说 从头开始 慢慢来
Okay... let me hear it.
Start at the beginning.
Take your time.
呃 Hector给了我这个地址
Uh, Hector gave me the address.
These guys regular customers?
- 这些人是常客吗? - 不 是第一次
No. First-timers.
这里我有很多生意 我和这家旅馆有协议
I do a lot of business here.
I got a deal with the hotel.
看
Look.
(sneezes)
我自己的古龙水 有序列号的 送给你
My own cologne. It's got my number.
Keep it.
好吧 我放弃
Yeah, it's okay. I'm gonna pass.
我...我下午在大厅和他见面
I... I met with him
in the lobby in the afternoon.
He said he wanted to surprise his friends, so...
他说他想给他的朋友一个惊喜 所以...
so he gave me a key.
所以他给我了房间钥匙
(crying): I came in through that door
我从那个门进来 就看到这副情形 除了...
and spotted them the way they are now,
except...
(sniffles)
除了什么?
Except what?
我很肯定 我第一次看到他时 他还长着头发
I'm pretty sure he had hair when I first met him.
Take it off.
拿掉
(sighs)
(bones cracking)
- 哦 - Duck?
Yeah.
Duck?
就是最锋利的剃刀
Even the sharpest of razors, on a-on a shave this close
在这么近的距离剃毛 也会引起须部假性毛囊炎 也叫...
would cause pseudofolliculitis barbae, aka...
- 剃刀伤痕 - 对
Razor burn.
Yeah.
但是 注意这个去疤痕术的裂缝
However,
note the complete lack of dermabrasive disruption.
不管谁做的 都是在他们死后才做的
Whoever did this did so
after they were dead.
单身汉1号 海军上士Jeff Ross 技术员 从韩国Muchuk基地退役
TONY: Bachelor number one is Marine Staff Sergeant Jeff Ross,
a mechanic on leave from Camp Muchuk in South Korea.
二号受害者 Eric Jurel 平民
Second victim: Eric Jurel, a civilian.
经营一家位于华盛顿的拍卖培训学校
Runs an auctioneering school in D.C.
嘉宾 Alan Sandich 五角大楼的底层文员
Guest of honor:
Alan Sandich, a low-level file clerk
at the Pentagon.
和他的未婚妻谈过吗?
Talk to the fiancée?
Uh, she's out of town,
她出城了 不过我们正在尽量联系上她
but we are working on getting ahold of her now.
(computer chirps)
No criminal records
没犯罪记录 除非把高中一年级时 亵渎教堂算上
across the board, unless you count
egging a church freshman year of high school.
These guys have known each other for a while.
这几个人都认识好久了
- 为什么要亵渎教堂? - 搞清楚它
Why would you egg a church?
Find out.
You got it, boss.
收到 老大
Tony, let's go.
Tony 走吧 跟着我
Follow me.
不 你跟着我
No, no, no. You follow me.
Don't fight your inner sidekick, McGee.
别和你亲密的同党争 这可不合适
It's unbecoming.
我可以把这句话原封不动的送回你
I could say the same thing to you.
是啊 你可不能因为 人人都知道同党要矮点 而且你...
No, you can't because
everyone knows that sidekicks are shorter, and you...
和你不差一厘
Are exactly the same height as you.
Look, you're not gonna make me say it, are you?
听着 你不是想让我这么说的 对吧?
- 你觉得自己太帅了不适合做人家同党? - 不是
You think you're too good-Iooking to be the sidekick?
是大家都觉得我很帅 尤其是女性同胞
No. People think I'm too good-Iooking.
Specifically, the women people.
实际上 我发现McGee更帅点
Actually, I find McGee to be the more handsome.
Nothing personal.
公正的说
Hi.
Hello.
你好
So, what are you doing here?
嗯 你来做什么?
David... with me.
David...跟我来
刚好回答了我的问题
That answers that question.
I have to go.
我得走了
Gibbs探员已经简单告诉我了 你想回来工作 是吗?
Agent Gibbs already briefed me.
You want back.
Is that right?
That is correct.
是的
你和你父亲讨论过了吗?
Have you discussed this with your father?
I am not sure how his opinion is relevant.
我不太肯定 他的想法和这有没有关系
是我们救了你 不是摩萨德 也不是你父亲
We rescued you.
Not Mossad, not your father.
I think it would be very relevant.
我认为这很有关系
Have I not been a valuable asset to NCIS?
对于NCIS 我是否还是一个有价值的存在呢?
Without question.
毫无疑问
那么问题到底是什么呢?
Then what is the problem?
David 你从来都不是探员 你是摩萨德的联络官
David, you were never an agent.
You were the Mossad liaison officer,
也就是说 你和摩萨德脱不了干系
which, by definition, requires you
to have a relationship with Mossad.
Have you even spoken to your father?
你都没和你父亲谈过?
No.
没有
You're damaged goods.
你非常优秀
How damaged I need to know
我要知道你够不够优秀 才能搞清楚我应该怎么处理你
before I can even begin to figure out what to do with you.
你通过了心理评估测试 我们再来谈
You pass a psych evaluation battery, and we'll talk.
Thank you.
- 谢谢 - David?
David.
No promises.
我可没做任何承诺
拍卖行的吆喝 对大多数人来说 听起来就像胡言乱语
The auction chant...
to most of the public, it's gibberish.
But it's actually carefully crafted to avoid
不过 实际上通过培训 可以避免给人考虑的时间
giving people time to think.
(crowd murmurs)
Thoughtful people spend less,
深思熟虑的人花的少 消费就是有规律的游戏
and spending is the name of the proverbial game.
Any questions?
- 还有问题吗? - 嗯 我有
Yeah. I have some.
我也有个问题
I have a question, as well.
Break down into teams of two and practice.
分成两组练习
Is this about Eric Jurel?
关于Eric Jurel?我听说了
I already heard.
- 好消息总是传的快啊 - 好消息?
Good news travels fast.
Good news?
他死了 对吧?
Well, he's dead, isn't he?
你想一大早醒来就做谋杀案的头号嫌疑犯?
Did you wake up this morning wanting to be the prime suspect
in a murder investigation?
如果盼着Eric Jurel死翘翘就让我变成嫌疑犯的话 这个拍卖学校的每个人都有份
If wishing Eric Jurel dead makes me a suspect,
then so is every employee of this auction school.
Eric took pleasure in making others miserable.
Eric总是把快乐建立在别人痛苦之上
没人会为他掉一滴泪
No one is shedding any tears for that man.
你肯定?
You sure about that?
哦 她叫Elaina 我们的杂货品经纪人
Ugh, that's Elaina, our miscellaneous items broker.
她可以把沙子卖到给一个阿拉伯人 然后再迷恋上他 把他烦死
She could sell sand to a Bedouin
and then bore him to death about her latest crush.
- 不用管她 - 我们的工作就是什么都管
Pay her no heed.
It's our job to heed.
你同意了这个购买价
ELAINA: You agreed to the purchase price.
Fine, if you don't want it, I know 20 people who will
好 如果你不想要的 我还有20个人想要 还有个律师等着告倒你
and a lawyer who will have your head.
(sighs)
我能为你做什么吗?
Can I help you?
是的 我想问你几个关于你老板的问题 你是Elaina 对吧?
Yes, um,
we'd like to ask you a few questions about your boss.
You're Elaina, right?
I assume you've heard the news?
- 我想 你已经知道这件事了吧? - 是的...
Yes.
太可怕了
It's terrible.
Were you two...
你们俩是不是...?
No.
不 我是说 我是的...
I mean, I was...
但他不是...
He wasn't...
我们不是一对
No, we weren't.
You know, it's not that there wasn't a spark.
也不是没有火花
It's just that he...
只是他有点...
你知道为什么有人想杀他吗?
Any reason that you can think of
why someone would want him dead?
很多人都误解了他
Well, a lot of people misunderstood him.
But Eric was a good man, deep down.
但内心深处 Eric是个好人
I can't see anyone wanting to hurt him.
我不明白为什么有人想要伤害他
(sniffles)
- 但是... - 但是什么?
But...
But what?
一次 我偶然听到他...
I... overheard him...
on the phone in the office.
在办公室讲电话
That he said he thought someone was following him.
他说 他觉得被人跟踪了
- 我从没参加过单身派对 - 是吗? 人生真不完整
I have never been to a bachelor party.
Really?
How sad.
我还是被邀请过
Well, I've been invited.
只是一次不舒服 另一次腿摔坏了
It's just, one time I was sick
and then another time I had a, uh, broken leg.
那我的单身派对故事绝对让你毛骨悚然
Well, I could tell you stories that would make your hair curl.
- 说来听听 - 免了 你最好别说 Duck
- Well, go on. - GIBBS: No.
- It's better he doesn't. Duck. - Oh, Jethro.
Jethro 我可以告诉他那次...
Can't I tell him about the time when...
还是免了
Better I don't.
叫你下来 是因为肝脏病理表明
Uh, I called you down here because liver pathology
suggested... and Abby later confirmed...
而且Abby确定 三人死前都被下了药
that all three men were drugged prior to their deaths.
The champagne.
下在香槟里
And while semi-conscious, one was drowned,
在半清醒之际 一人被溺死 另一人被闷死
one suffocated, and Sergeant Ross here
Ross上士则死于酒精中毒
died of a massive alcohol poisoning.
Likely ingested under duress.
很可能是被人灌的
Semi-conscious?
半清醒状态?
Very astute, Jethro.
Jethro 凶手很聪明 他想...
- The killer... - Wanted them
在他们还算清醒时 杀了他们
awake when they died.
这提示凶手可能在进行什么仪式
Which implies a deeper meaning
to the ritualistic manner of their deaths.
Palmer也发现了些疑点
Mr. Palmer here discovered something.
我在Ross的军队档案中发现了矛盾之处
I found an inconsistency in Ross's military file.
档案中说 他在韩国基地时受了工伤
The record states that he sustained an injury
during a work-related accident
on base in Korea, but Dr. Mallard
Mallard医生却发现了枪弹伤证据
found evidence of a gunshot wound.
我想工伤应该不会出现这个吧
Not something I'd expect to see in a work-related injury.
Falsified the report.
篡改报告
It's a good assumption.
不错的猜测
(傻麦)
Hey, boss.
老大 你好
Uh, ATM and traffic cameras...
在看提款机和交通录像 有线索说其中一个受害者被跟踪了
we got a tip that one of our victims
was, uh, being followed.
Thought I'd check on some of the routes he was on.
我想查下他去过的地儿 看看到底是谁在跟踪他
See if we could find out who the tail was.
刚才我甩手是...
Yeah, the swiping thing was...
我们得和Ross上士在韩国的上级谈谈
Need to talk to Sergeant Ross's C.O.
- in South Korea. - I'll set it up and...
- 我会安排好 并且... - DiNozzo去哪了?
- Where's DiNozzo? - On an interview.
在做审讯 Alan Sandich的未婚妻回来了
Alan Sandich's fiancée's back in town.
而且 她已经再订婚了
And she's already reengaged.
你有没有想到谁 老大?
Does it remind you of anyone, boss?
这种玩笑还要开多久 DiNozzo?
How long are you gonna keep making those jokes, DiNozzo?
I think that was actually the last time
我保证是最后一次 抱歉
I'm ever gonna make that joke.
Sorry.
她就再订婚了? 才过了24小时
She's engaged already?
It's only been 24 hours.
也不完全是这样 看看这个
Not exactly.
Check this out.
(music playing, men chattering)
Wow.
That's illegal in most states.
其实这在很多州都算违法 在欧洲有些地方 你甚至可以...
There's parts of Europe you can...
这种行为有伤风化
It's bad behavior.
(clears throat)
- 这来自Sandich的单身派对 - 关掉
This is from Sandich's bachelor party.
GIBBS: Turn it off.
这才是他真正的单身派对
Yeah, it's his real bachelor party.
发生在五月前
Five months ago.
When Sandich's fiancée
Sandich的未婚妻发现了这录像带 于是取消了婚约
found the tape, she called off the engagement.
She hasn't seen him since.
- 从那后 再也没见过他 - 这就是说...
Which means...
They were all still single.
他们还是单身
第二次单身派对只是个幌子
Second bachelor party was just a cover.
Cover for what?
什么的幌子?
我听过替单身派对打幌子的 没听过拿来当幌子的
TONY: I've heard of a cover story for a bachelor party,
but I've never heard of one being the cover story.
你觉得他们真正的意图是什么?
What do you think they were really up to?
通常而言 不是什么好东西
The usual.
No good.
Any luck on whoever's following Eric Jurel,
找到是谁在跟踪拍卖屋老板Eric Jurel吗?
our auction house owner?
No, and it was over a week ago.
没有 而且这是一周前的事
ZIVA: Could try to recreate your victim's daily route
可以试着用受害人手机的GPS历史 重建他的行程表
by using his cell's GPS history.
Then see if there are any other cell phones consistently
看看在这些区域 是否有可疑号码出现
in the same area.
If so...
- 这样的话... - 我们就找到Jurel的跟屁虫了
We've got Jurel's tail.
I'm sorry.
不好意思 我不小心听到你们谈话
I overheard you two talking.
不必 我还得说谢谢 这方法很有用
No, thank you, 'cause that is extremely helpful.
我们可以调出GPS历史 查看记录
I mean, we can pull the GPS history and look at the logs.
And I'm gonna go do that
我去吃块奶油果仁饼干 再做这个
after I get a Nutter Butter.
Taking the tour?
在四处参观吗?
I have my first psych evaluation.
我刚去做了第一次精神状态评定
Oh, yeah, I always love those.
- 我很喜欢做这个 - 当然了
I'm sure.
You get to talk about yourself the entire time.
那里 你可以一直谈论自己
(chuckles)
I'm sorry, I meant, um...
抱歉 我是想说...
No, no, no, that's okay.
没关系
No one's ever accused you of having tact.
机敏圆滑 可不会被人称作缺点
Sorry.
抱歉
(phone ringing)
Sorry, I gotta take this.
抱歉 我得接 可能与工作有关
It's work. (clears throat)
DiNozzo.
我是DiNozzo 听着 我已经拿到...
Listen, I've got...
For you.
是找你的
Hello.
- 你好 - Ziva 你说过要来实验室的
ABBY: Ziva, you said you were coming down to the lab.
Yes, sorry, Abby.
- 是的 Abby 我很抱歉 - 现在下来
- I know I said I would. - Come now.
All right, I will be right down.
好的 这就下来
Haven't had your private Abby welcome yet, huh?
看来还没享受过Abby的私人迎接啊
Careful, she might give you a 21-gun salute.
小心她给你来个21发加农炮欢迎礼 (21-gun salute 盛大的欢迎仪式)
I will, um...
那我... 再来找你
see you later.
我就在这儿
I will be right here.
(hard rock music playing)
Hello, Abby.
你好 Abby
(music stops)
What the hell is wrong with you?!
你到底有什么毛病?
一起经历那么多 你怎么还会怀疑Tony?
How could you have doubted Tony
after everything you've been through together?
你真觉得Tony杀Rivkin是出于嫉妒?
You really think that Tony killed Rivkin
because he was jealous?
- Abby, please calm... - You weren't thinking.
- Abby 冷静... - 你大脑进水了 肯定是这样
That's right. You weren't thinking.
尽管我也能理解你的初衷
Although I suppose I could understand
your initial reaction.
虽然当时你感情失控 行事草率
You were in an emotional time for you, and people act rashly.
但你真的告诉Gibbs 不相信Tony吗?
But to tell Gibbs that you didn't trust Tony?!
Which I guess I also could understand, you know.
虽然这我也可以理解
毕竟 他向你男朋友开了枪
I mean, he did just shoot your boyfriend.
In your living room.
就在你房里 杀死了他
To death.
你可以以此作为借口
All right, l-I'll give you that one.
But this is Tony we're talking about here!
但我们说的是Tony啊!
外表软弱不羁 内心却硬如磐石的Tony
AII... all soft and goofy on the outside
and 100% rock on the inside.
尽管你指责他这些 他还是冒生命危险救你出来!
And after everything you accused him of,
he risked his life to go save you!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
你真该感到羞耻!
Even though, in hindsight,
尽管回过头想想 整件事也不是那么无理
it is starting to make a little bit more sense now.
但不管怎样 皮球已经踢到了你那边
But either way, the ball is in your court.
Tony目前1比0领先
It is Tony one and Ziva zilch.
This is your move.
轮到你了 你最好给我好好动起来
And it better be a good one.
God, I was so worried about you.
天哪 我太担心你了
(sighs)
I know.
我都懂
(beeps, noise makers popping)
欢迎 ZIVA 回家
Nice to speak to you in person, Agent Gibbs.
很高兴能和你面谈 特别探员Gibbs
I'm sure I'm not the first to say, "ooh-rah."
我肯定我不是第一个说"好哇"的人
Quite a feat your team pulled off in North Africa.
你们在北非的功绩让人景仰
Uh-huh.
能告诉我些细枝末节就好了
Love to hear the details.
Come on, Gunny.
说嘛 老兄 在韩国基本没什么行动
We don't get a lot of action in South Korea.
Ross上士 有印象吗?
Sergeant Ross... you know him?
好人一个 我能帮你什么?
He's a good man.
How can I help?
你签的事故报告说 他在基地伤了自己?
Accident report you signed said he hurt himself on base?
He was a flight mechanic.
他是个飞机技工 一次因为液压伤了胳膊
Got his arm caught in a hydraulic.
是吗? 我的法医说是枪弹伤 他不常犯错
Really?
My M.E. here says it was a gunshot wound.
He's pretty smart.
You care to revise your report?
你不惜篡改报告?
(sighs): Guess I have to.
我不得不这样
慢慢发现 Ross是我遇到最可恶的混蛋
Starting with the fact Ross was actually
the biggest bastard I'd ever met.
Why would you falsify a report?
你为什么要篡改报告?
Was trying to avoid an international incident.
努力不引起国际争端
Ross took two days of leave.
Ross请了两天假 去见他首尔的情人
Said he was visiting his girl in Seoul.
When he came back, he'd been shot.
回来时 就被射伤了
Husband?
- 被情人老公打伤? - 他是这么说的
That's what he said.
我给了他口头警告 掩埋了事实
I gave him a verbal reprimand and buried it.
Geopolitics here are dicey.
这里的地方特色
Not gonna win hearts and minds going after another man's tail.
捉人小尾巴不放 可不会使你受欢迎
我需要修正后的报告
I'm gonna need a revised report.
明早八点给你
I'll have it on your desk at 0800 tomorrow.
I got something for you to sign.
有一些文件得要你签字
Ziva's reinstatement.
Ziva的复职同意书
她通过了第一次精神状态评定吗?
She passed her first psych eval?
这么说吧 她没挂
She didn't fail; let's put it that way.
Saleem's men put a world of hurt on her,
虽然Saleem的手下折磨她很久 但她依然生存
but I think she's viable.
What's Eli David think?
Eli David怎么想?
I got some details to work out.
我还有点其他工作要做
Not gonna try if you don't want her.
但要是你不想要她 我就不管这些了
Or were you hoping that I couldn't work out the details
或者你根本不想去做这些工作 这样的话你就不用打给Eli?
so you wouldn't even have to make that call?
I already told you, Leon.
我已经说过 Leon 我们离不开Ziva
We need Ziva.
我记得
Yeah... I remember.
Well, that should make it easy for you.
这样的话 对你来说就更简单了
Sergeant Ross went MIA during a two-day leave last month.
Ross上士在上月的两天离开中行程不明
Find out where he went.
- 找出来他去哪了 - 在韩国?
In South Korea?
Okay, I'll just make some phone calls.
好的 看来我只有打几通电话了
Order me some Berlitz CDs.
给我买几盘Berliz的教程 (Berliz CDs 语言教程)
头 我知道该怎么找出 是谁在跟踪拍卖屋伙计Jurel 了
Hey, boss, I think we've got a way to find out
who was tailing Jurel, the auction house guy.
The red line was Jurel's daily drive before he died.
红线是Jurel死前的日常行程
我们寻找覆盖这个范围的手机信号
We're looking for cell signals that were shadowing him.
事实上 这是Ziva的主意
It was actually Ziva's idea.
We weren't discussing the case.
当时我们没在谈案件 她只是偶然经过
She just walked by.
- (computer beeping) - I got a hit.
有线索了 是个手机号码
It's a cell phone.
Shows up close to Jurel's car several times.
多次接近Jurel的车
You got a name?
- 知道是谁的吗? - 很奇怪
That is odd.
这手机没有电子序列编码 也没人注册
Well, cell doesn't have a valid ESN number.
It's not registered with any carrier.
可能是黑市来
Could be black market.
是部一次性手机 Tim 说一次性手机就行了
It's a burn phone, Tim. Just say burn phone.
Can you trace it?
能追踪吗?
不仅如此 我还能带你们去那
I can do better than that; I can take you right to it.
(tires screech)
(device beeping)
It's inside.
在里面
With me, McGee.
跟我来 McGee
In position.
- 准备好了 - 听我指示
GIBBS (over radio): On my mark.
Go.
行动
MAN (quietly): Baltimore Police.
巴尔的摩警察 发现两名嫌犯
Got two suspects.
我是海军罪犯调查署的
(whispering): NCIS.
Got a call: shots fired.
接到报警 有人开枪 在小巷里 我搭档已经控制一个嫌犯
Partner's got one suspect in the alley.
DiNozzo.
- DiNozzo - Gibbs
Gibbs.
Shelley.
叫我Shelley 看来现在是他负责
Guessing he's in charge now.
你猜对了
Good guess.
Is Friendly still on the force?
Friendly还在你们局吗?
Retired last year.
去年退休了
DiNozzo 等等 你就是Tony DiNozzo?
DiNozzo... Wait, are you Tony DiNozzo?
- 欠你钱就不是 - 你不欠我钱
Only if I don't owe you money.
You don't.
很高兴能有你掩护我
Just glad to have you at my back, sir.
Clear.
- 没人 - 没人
(whispers): Clear.
Jurel的跟踪者曾待过这里 他走了
Jurel's tail was here. He's gone now.
- (clattering) - This guy...
Officer Shelley?
Shelley警官?
It's locked.
锁上了
(car starts)
(tires screeching)
McGEE: There's nothing in back.
后面什么都没有 后巷没人
Alley was empty.
Couldn't find the partner.
找不到搭档
因为根本没有什么搭档
That's because he was never here.
This is Shelley's house.
这就是Shelley的房子
TONY (in deep voice): There are three men murdered
三个男人在假单身派对上被谋杀
at a fake bachelor party.
What were they really doing there?
他们到底在那里做了些什么? 没有人知道
No one knows.
This is definitely the cell that was tailing Jurel.
可以肯定的是这手机是用来跟踪Jurel的
If Shelley was working a case,
要是Shelley办过某个案子 巴尔的摩警察局会不知道吗
Baltimore PD doesn't know about it.
(in deep voice): Still, no one knows.
仍然没人知道
(stifled squeal)
(normal voice): What we do know is
我们只知道Shelley曾跟踪过受害者
that Shelley was tailing the victims.
Uh, found those under his bed.
- 在他床下发现了这些东西 - 不是跟踪...是瞄准
Not tailing... targeting.
Spending a lot of time at airports.
在机场花了太多时间
Well, there's nothing useful on the cell itself,
手机本身没有有用信息 但是这种型号售价超过一千块
but the model retails for over a grand.
Yeah, that's not bad on a cop's salary.
以警察的薪水来说这手机算很不错了
We found this on his computer.
我们在他电脑里发现了这个
- Suicide note. - Rambling.
- 遗书 - 杂乱无章
Says, uh, he's sorry; doesn't say why.
恩 他说很抱歉 但没说为什么
We interrupted the second half of a murder-suicide?
我们阻止了畏罪自杀的后半截?
Well, let's not hang around and find out. DiNozzo.
别闲着 赶紧去查DiNozzo
I will, uh, contact my buddies at the Baltimore PD,
好的 我会和巴尔的摩警察局的兄弟联系 看看他们是否知道Shelley在哪
- see if they know where Shelley was headed. - McGee.
I'll look into Shelley's background,
McGee
我去查Shelley的背景 看他和受害者之间是否有联系
see if there's any connection between him and the victims.
Thanks.
谢谢
Hey.
McGee.
McGee 你在休息?
You taking a break?
I was on my way to the office,
我在上班的路上 准备去买杯咖啡
came to get a coffee, saw you sitting here,
thought I'd come say hello.
看见你坐在这里 我想应该去打个招呼
I was actually coming to look for you.
其实我刚好想找你
I wanted to say...
我想说...谢谢
thank you.
Did you come to the navy yard just to say thanks or?
你来海军基地只是为了说谢谢还是...
I am, uh, finishing my psych evaluation with
我今天完成了医生Bracco的精神评估
Dr. Bracco today.
Janice Bracco, with the?
Janice Bracco 有着...
Man hands and the pretty eyes, yes.
男人手掌和漂亮眼睛 怎么了?
Why?
Um, nothing, no.
没有 没
(sighs)
So how's it going?
评估说什么?
I will not deny
我不会否认过去三个月所发生的...
these past three months have been...
a challenge.
是个挑战
But that was all in the past, and the past is the past.
但这些都是过去的事情 过去的已经过去
Is it?
是吗?
Yes.
对
So why are you avoiding Tony?
你为什么避开Tony?
Hey, boss, when did you get back?
嘿 老大 你什么时候回来的?
Ten minutes ago.
10分钟以前
Just, uh, taking a...
Coffee break?
- 只是... - 咖啡时间
Yeah.
对
Hey, I found a connection
嘿 我发现Shelley警官和受害者之间的联系了
between Officer Shelley and our dead guys.
They went to the same high school.
他们上过同一所高中
Yeah, how'd you know?
你怎么知道的?
Uh, there is more.
恩 还有
The records say that our dead guys
记录上说死者曾恃强欺弱
had a history of bullying.
Shelley was their favorite target.
Shelley曾是他们最爱的目标
Mm, they brutalized him.
他们喜欢凌辱他
Gives us motive,
我们有了杀人动机 假设他这些年都满怀怨恨
assuming that he held a grudge all these years.
And if he didn't, it recently got a refresh,
就算他没有 但最近他又想了起来 上完厕所我会来解释
and I'm going to explain that after I hit the head.
DiNozzo.
- DiNozzo - 我可以等
It can wait.
(sighs)
I spoke to a buddy from Homicide,
我和凶杀组的一个老兄谈了 他说Shelly一个月前拦下过Ross上士的车
and he said that Shelley pulled over Sergeant Ross
about a month ago and gave him a ticket,
给了他一张罚单 但发现他是他高中时代的噩梦时
and then ended up giving him three tickets
once he realized it was his old high school tormentor.
他一下给了他三张罚单
Oh, I bet that felt good.
- 哦 我猜那一定很爽 - 你当然会那么想
You would think that.
Fun didn't last long.
快乐并没有持续太久 你为什么不检查你的邮件?
Why don't you check your e-mail.
(Tony grunts)
Ross got payback.
Ross进行了报复
E-mailed an old high school video
给管辖区每个人都发了一份 Shelley以前高中的录象
of Shelley to everyone in Shelley's precinct.
Turn that off! Turn that off!
关掉! 把那个关掉!
Not the sort of thing you want your buddies to see.
这可不是你希望朋友看到的东西
(indistinct chatter over video)
- Oh, yeah. - (laughter over video)
(indistinct chatter)
- (screeches) - Hold on.
Smile for the camera, baby.
对着相机笑笑 宝贝 他象个和尚
(over video): He looks like a monk.
GIBBS: I've seen that before.
我以前见过
Yeah, at our murder scene.
在我们的谋杀现场
Boss, I think Shelley was recreating
头 我想Shelley是在重现他过去遇到的事情
incidents from his past.
Look at our dead guy with the head in the toilet.
- 看看死者的头在厕所里的样子 - 厕所
- Toilet. - Was a weekly occurrence
for Shelley.
对Shelley来说那是每周都发生的事
Jurel and his buddies at prom
Jurel和他的兄弟在舞会上强迫Shelley 喝酒喝到挂 和Ross警官一样
forced Shelley to drink until he got sick, same as Sergeant Ross.
But their favorite pastime was stuffing Shelley's head
但他们最爱的活动是把Shelly的头塞进他的背包里
into his backpack.
Yeah, I'd say
好吧 我得说Shelley这 些年确实满怀怨恨
Shelley held a grudge all these years.
- We got motive. - And opportunity.
- 我们有了谋杀动机 - 还有机会
Be nice to have Shelley.
抓住了Shelley更好
McGee,
- bank statements, credit cards. - Yeah.
- McGee 查银行报表 信用卡 - 好
DiNozzo.
Yes, boss?
- DiNozzo - 在 老大
- Shake it. - Thank you, boss.
- 去厕所吧 - 谢谢 头 哦 我的天
(grunting): Oh, God.
♪ Which my father bought ♪
*这就是我父亲用两个Zuzim买来的*
♪ For two zuzim ♪
♪ Chad gadya... ♪
* Chad gadya...*(犹太歌曲)
(humming)
How long you been standing there?
你在那里站了多久?
Long enough to see that you are well hydrated
够长知道你从沙漠回来后 充分得到了水的滋润
after your time in the desert.
And the thinking behind surprising me?
你想吓我玩吗?
(zips)
I was not sure what to say.
我不知道该说什么
But you were sure it had to be
但你既然在男厕所就必须要说点什么
said in the men's room.
I'm sure it had to be said.
我是要说
When you shot Michael,
当你对Michael开枪时 我几乎杀了站着的你
I almost killed you where you stood.
I wasn't standing.
- 我没站着 - 对 你没有
No, you weren't.
You were lying on the ground
你躺在地板上没有其他支援 完全违背了规则
without adequate backup, completely violating protocol.
And double-parked.
- 还违章停车 - 对 我注意到了
Yes, I noticed.
But that does not matter.
但那没关系
Just like it does not matter how it worked out for Michael.
就像对于Michael是怎么想的也不重要了
So what does?
那又怎么样呢?
That you had my back.
你在掩护我
That you have always had my back
你一直都在掩护我 所以我...
and that I was...
wrong... to question your motives.
我不应该怀疑你的动机
So why did you?
你为什么怀疑我?
I trusted my brother Ari.
我相信过我的哥哥Ari 我也相信过Michael
I trusted Michael.
I could not afford to trust you.
我已经没有气力去相信你
I thought you weren't sure what to say.
我想你还没想好要说什么
Guess I had a long time to think about things.
我有足够的时间来思考
I'm sorry, Ziva.
- 对不起 Ziva - 不
No.
It is I who am sorry.
该说抱歉的人是我
Your instincts were right.
你的直觉是对的
You were a cop,
你曾是警察 我不该怪你按警察的思路办事
and I should have never faulted you for thinking like one.
I'm a cop.
我是警察 我按警察的思路办事
I think like a cop.
Genius.
天才
I know how to find Officer Shelley.
我知道怎么找Shelley警官了
Track his burn phone.
追踪他的手机
Well, we already know where it is.
我们都知道它在哪里 它在证据库
It's in the evidence garage.
He's got another one.
他又弄了一个
Well, that's great,
but without the cells' ESN numbers,
好 但是没有手机电子序号 我们无法进行追踪
we can't track any of 'em.
Think, McSidekick.
想想看 麦同党 发挥你的力量 使用你的能力
Use the leading man.
Harness those powers.
Okay.
好
It was an unregistered phone.
这是个没登记的手机
It was pricey
- 对警察来说很贵 - 对
- for a cop. - Bingo.
Shelley took it from a bust.
Shelley偷用赃物
Happens all the time.
这样的事很常见
An extra Rolex
证据库里经常会不见了 劳力士或笔记本电脑
or laptop disappears from the evidence locker,
not that I've ever done anything like that.
我从没干过这样的事
Officer Shelley busted a black-market cell phone ring
Shelley警官去年查处了一批黑市手机 而且...
last year, and...
...the impounded cells' ESN numbers are all logged.
被没收手机的电子序号都有记录 要是他拿了一个 我们就能追踪到
If he's got one, we can track it.
See if any are active.
看是否有在用的
We got one of 'em.
我们找到了一个
Making a call right now.
正在拨出电话
(phone ringing)
Boss, you may want to answer that.
老大 你也许想去接
Yeah. Gibbs.
- 对 - 让我跟DiNozzo谈谈
SHELLEY (over phone): Let me talk to DiNozzo.
TONY: I'm here.
我在这里
I know how it looks.
我知道这看起来像什么
I shouldn't have run,
but l-I didn't kill those guys.
我不应该跑 但我没有杀那些人
You draw the line at criminal stalking?
可你拒绝承认跟踪过他?
I was following 'em, yeah.
我是跟踪过他
Some kind of deal was going down; I wanted the details.
我们的合作失败了 我想要知道详情
You wanted payback.
你想要报复
The plan was just to take their pot of gold,
我的计划只是想拿走他们的钱 然后以牙还牙而已
hit 'em where it hurts.
I didn't kill anybody.
我没有杀人 我是被陷害的
I was set up.
(over phone): Well, then,
那你干脆过来吧 我是个好听众
why don't you just come on in? I'm a good listener.
I assume you got my location
我想你们现在确定了我的地点
- by now. - (typing)
- (computer beeps) - Yeah.
对
Phone booth
by the newsstand on K Street.
K大街报摊旁的电话亭 一个人来
Come alone.
Thing belongs in a museum.
- 博物馆里才会出现的玩意 - McGee
GIBBS (over radio): McGee.
Yeah, ready.
对 准备好了
Oh, boy.
哦 伙计 出来 我得用下电话
(snoring)
All right, hop out of there.
I got to use the phone.
(grunts)
(tires squealing)
Here they come,
他们来了 DiNozzo.
DiNozzo.
(squealing continues)
Oh, yeah, yeah, I see 'em.
哦 对 我看见他们了
(squealing continues)
Uh-oh.
Come on, we got to go.
快点 我们得走了 快 快走
- (squealing continues) - Come on!
Here we go, now!
(squealing continues)
- You okay? - Yeah.
- 你没事吧? - 对
I got something wet in my hands,
我手上沾了些湿湿的东西 但我不想知道是什么
but I don't want to think about it.
(crowd chattering)
枪手靠的很近 直线射程
Shooter was pretty close.
- Point-blank range. - Witness saw
有人走近了车 听见枪击声 枪手逃走
someone approach the car, heard the shot, shooter took off.
那意味着Shelley认识袭击者
Which suggests that Officer Shelley knew his attacker.
Said he was set up.
那就是说他是被陷害的
Well, his presence here would tend to confirm that.
他在这里就证明了这个事实
But set up by who?
是谁陷害他?
Someone who knew his past.
某个知道他过去的人
Making it appear
让他看起来像是跟踪和谋杀了仇人
that he stalked and murdered his tormenters.
Hey.
我们从Shelley追踪的 神秘交易上得到了线索
We got a lead on the mystery deal Shelley was tracking.
It's from Sergeant Ross's C.O. in Korea.
这是Ross上士位于韩国的指挥官提供的
It's a report of a shooting
这是一份在非军事区发生枪击的报告 那有一个用于走私的机场
near the DMZ at an airstrip used by smugglers.
C.O. thinks that's where Ross
指挥官认为Ross是在那里待了两天
went on his two-day leave.
枪击之后 卫星追踪到飞机离开 失去了联系
After the shooting, SATCOM tracked the plane leaving,
lost contact.
你们认为Ross在飞机上放了东西?
Think Ross had a package on that plane?
对
He had something.
We want to find out what,
我们想查出那是什么 还有是谁杀了他...
we need to find out who killed Officer...
(sneezes)
- 祝你好运 - 谢谢
- Bless you. - Thank you.
Shelley Shelley警官
Shelley. Officer Shelley.
I think it's something on the body.
- 我想尸体上有什么东西 - 对 古龙香水
Yes, cologne.
他最近一定和使用古龙水的人接触过
He must have come into contact
recently with an overcologner.
I was just about to take a sample
我刚要给Abby送样本去分析 我们...
up to Abby for analysis.
We...
我在古龙水上做宣传 那也是犯罪吗?
So I advertise on cologne bottles.
Is that a crime?
- 应该是 - 真不敢相信 业余的家伙
- Should be. - Can't believe this.
Amateur hour here.
我调查过的记录 结果是他是很有...
McGEE: I looked into Hector's records.
Turns out
he is a man of many... (sneezes)
A man of many talents.
很有才能的人 对不起 老大
Sorry, boss.
脱衣舞者只是幌子 他其实是倒卖赃物的人
Strippers are just his cover.
He's actually a fence.
从未被判刑 但被怀疑倒卖的东西从 盗版DVD到飞毛腿导弹零件
Never been convicted
but suspected of fencing everything from bootleg DVDs
to SCUD missile parts.
他现在在倒卖什么?
What's he fencing now?
(sighs softly)
How'd you get the shiner?
你眼下的伤口怎么来的?
我剃须时不小心割伤了
I cut myself shaving.
他指甲里有你的DNA
Your DNA underneath his fingernails.
He came by this morning, then he left.
他早上是过来了 然后离开 就这些
End of story.
One body not good enough
死一个人还不够 对吗 硬汉?
for you, tough guy? 'Cause I got
我这还有三具尸体呢!
three more right here!
我与此无关 我和警察也是这么说的
I had nothing to do with this
and I told the cop the same thing.
Why was he asking you?
他为什么问你?
You've got the right to remain silent.
你有权保持沉默
Anything you say will be used against you
- 但你所说的将成为呈堂证供... - 等一下 等等 等等
- in a court... - Wait, wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Jurel因为一件大事来找我
Jurel came to me with something big.
The plane out of Korea... it had a package on it.
在韩国的飞机 有个大包裹
The package was the plane.
飞机就是那个包裹
Jurel's buddies fudged some paperwork,
Jurel的哥们伪造文书 将黑手触及到即将退役的军方运输机
got their hands on a military cargo plane
scheduled for decommissioning.
Jurel想让我销赃 值几百万美元
Jurel wanted me to fence it.
Worth a couple million.
They went to the hotel to celebrate.
他们去宾馆庆祝 我的姑娘去了
My girl shows up. She's only supposed to do
她只是去跳舞的 作为我私人的致谢 并拿个包裹
her dance as a token of my appreciation
and pick up a package.
The lock codes for the plane.
飞机密锁的解码
And then you know what she found instead.
你已经知道她发现了什么
Officer Shelley.
Shelley警官
Next thing I know, cop shows up at my door.
下一件事 是警察出现在我门前
Roughs me up
暴打我一顿 说我陷害他杀人
and accuses me of setting him up for murder.
And he just lets you go?
他就这么让你走了?
是的 当我对他说了同样的话后
Yeah, after I told him exactly what I'm telling you.
他抓错人了
He got the wrong guy.
And I got
Pubis俱乐部有五十个人能证明此事
about 50 people at Club Pubis
that can testify to that.
Well, it's not quite 50, but, uh, close enough.
没50人 不过也差不多
Club Pubis is a strip club.
Pubis是个脱衣舞俱乐部 Hector MCs周四晚上都在那
Hector MCs there on Thursday nights.
There's at least a dozen people
谋杀时至少有十几个人能证明他在那
that can put him there at the time of the murders.
So we are back to: who killed the cop?
我们还是回到谁杀了警察这里
And...
还有为何使用一把古董手枪作案
why they used an antique percussion cap pistol to do it.
I ran ballistics on the bullet that killed Officer Shelley.
我利用弹道鉴定击毙Shelley警官的子弹
- It was a new bullet fired from an old gun. - How old?
这是从老枪里打出的新子弹
有多老?
It was from a 19th century VR tower pistol.
这是19世纪的VR tower手枪
I know a shooting range nearby
我知道附近有个不错的射击场 你可以去
- where you can take that for a spin. - What?
什么? 射击? 这是古董 不是普通的廉价左轮
Spin?
This is a fine antique,
not some cheap revolver.
把你的高级古董放在后备箱?
Keep all your fine antiques in the trunk?
No.
不 我最近发现它在库存中不翼而飞
I recently discovered it missing from inventory.
我曾怀疑是被盗 并且..
I suspected it was stolen.
And... I've been looking for it.
- 试着寻找它 - 这不是找到了吗
And there it is.
Yeah, it works out nicely for us
自从它成了凶器后 对我们也有贡献
since that gun was used in a murder.
(chuckles) Uh...
- this isn't my car. - GIBBS: Yeah, we know that.
- 这不是我的车 - 我们知道 是Elaina的 她在哪?
It's Elaina's.
Where is she?
我 我给她打电话了
l-l-I just called her.
我说和她在这碰面 解释一下
I said to meet me out here to explain this.
She hasn't had time to dump it yet.
她没时间扔掉这玩意
Look who's here, boss.
老大 看看谁在这
- (sighs) - See, you run away like that,
你那么溜走看着很有嫌疑 Marcus小姐
it kind of makes you look guilty,
Miss Marcus.
- 有什么嫌疑? - 谋杀
Guilty of what?
- Murder. - Always said she was trouble.
我说过她很难搞
She found out about a deal your boss had going down.
她发现你老板的肮脏交易
你和Shelley警官搭伙
You partnered with Officer Shelley.
然后你背叛了他 自己独吞钱财
Then you double-crossed him
and kept the payday for yourself.
陷害Shelley警官谋杀
Set Shelley up for murder.
(laughs)
What's so funny?
有什么可笑的?
You haven't arrested me.
你们还没拘捕我
Means you don't have any proof.
- 说明你们没证据 - 麦证据
McProof.
Fake suicide note
我们在Shelley电脑里发现的假遗书
we found on Shelley's computer...
我们追踪该蠕虫病毒来自你的手提电脑
we traced the worm that planted that back to your laptop.
证明你杀了Jurel 他哥们和Shelley
Proves you killed Jurel, his buddies, and Shelley.
Uh-oh.
你知道那意味着什么
You know what that means.
- You're under arrest. - You're under arrest.
- 你被捕了 - 你被捕了
(Elaina groans)
You're a bad little putty tat.
你可真是只麻烦小猫
Where'd boss go?
- 老大去哪了? - 不知道
I don't know.
我们必须谈谈
We need to talk.
坐吧
Sit down.
When I came to see you and said
我来见你 说想回来
I wanted back...
你说是主任的命令
you said it was the director's call.
But I sensed your hesitation.
但我觉察到你的犹豫
现在仍是
I sense it now.
Even though I...
即使我认为自己说明白了
thought I made myself clear.
我理解你在以色列做的一切
I understand
- what you did in Israel... - Your brother
你的哥哥Ari
Ari.
你知道那晚发生的事
You know what happened that night.
It was here.
- 是在这里 - 我想听你说出来
I want to hear it from you.
你收到命令通过杀你哥哥 来取得我的信任
You had orders to kill your brother to earn my trust?
Yes.
是的
That's a problem.
那可是个大问题
You don't understand.
- 你不明白 - 你说的真没错 我不懂!
You're damn right I don't understand.
当我自愿执行那任务时...
- When I volunteered for that mission... - You killed
你杀了自己的亲哥哥 Ziva!
your own brother, Ziva!
我是希望我父亲错怪了Ari
It was because I hoped my father was wrong about Ari
and I did not want someone else blindly following orders.
而且我不希望别人被命令误导
我自愿去保护他的 Gibbs
I volunteered to protect him, Gibbs.
- You lied to me. - No, when I told you
- 你骗我 - 不 当我告诉你Ari是清白的 我相信
Ari was innocent, I believed it.
但是 没错
But yes.
I would have lied to you.
我当时可以骗你的
He was my brother.
他是我哥哥
而你什么都不是
And you were nothing.
But I was wrong about Ari.
但我错认了Ari 还有你
And you.
When I pulled the trigger to save your life,
当我开枪为了救你时 我没遵守指令
I was not following orders.
I mean, how could you even think?
我是说 你怎么能认为...
He was my brother.
他是我哥哥
现在他死了
And now he is gone.
Eli is all but dead to me.
Eli是我唯一的亲人 但对我来说什么也不是
我认为与我最亲近
And the closest thing I have...
最像父亲的一个人...
...to a father...
却在指控我
...is accusing me.
Okay.
好的
直奔机场
Headed straight to the airport.
Yeah, well, that's why they call it a go bag, honey,
这就是所谓的逃难包 宝贝儿 我一直放在后备箱
and I keep it in the trunk of my car.
Yeah, all right.
好的 一下飞机我就给你打电话
I'Il-I'll call you as soon as I land.
Yeah, uh...
- 好的... - 我爱你
(over phone): I love you.
I love you, too.
我也爱你 (谐音:我爱你们两个)
(over phone): Bye.
- 拜拜 - 好的
All right.
(elevator bell dings)
走吧
Moving on.
So how was your date
昨晚和精神病医生的约会如何 麦密欧?
with the, uh, shrink last night, McRomeo?
你觉得我会告你吗?
Think I'm gonna tell you?
说出我想知道的一切吧
Tells me everything I need to know.
很复杂的 Bracco医生是Ziva的...
It's actually pretty complicated.
Dr. Bracco is Ziva's...
Ziva的谁?
Ziva's what?
Ziva在这呢
Ziva's here.
(keyboard clicking)